<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Eric W. Jones</title>
    <link>https://erijones.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Eric W. Jones</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://erijones.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>My email address is jones.eric93 [at] gmail.com. I would love to talk to anyone interested in learning more about my research.
You can also follow me on twitter at @e_w_jones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/notes/</guid>
      <description>Here is a collection of miscellaneous notes:
Learning information theory with hangman. For a game of hangman with a three-letter word, in which X is the probability space of the first letter (26 elements) and Y is the probability space of the last two leters (26^2 elements), I consider various information theoretic quantities (e.g. joint entropy H(X,Y), conditional entropy H(Y|X), and the mutual information I(X;Y)). Updated 11/26/20.
Implementation of artificial boundary conditions in simulations of the 1D and 2D Fokker-Planck equations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/pictures/</guid>
      <description>Since 2016 I have had the pleasure of through-hiking the Colorado Trail (Fall 2017), the Wonderland Trail (Fall 2019), and the John Muir Trail (Fall 2020). Here are a few pictures from those adventures.
John Muir Trail (Fall 2020)                      
Colorado Trail (Fall 2017)                                            </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Everyone has a gut microbiome, full of trillions of microbes, that influences our health. One person&amp;rsquo;s microbiome might give them a stomach ache, while another person&amp;rsquo;s might help them metabolize food more efficiently. I want to figure out how &amp;ldquo;medicine for the microbiome&amp;rdquo; works&amp;ndash; how can a sick person&amp;rsquo;s microbiome be made &amp;ldquo;healthy&amp;rdquo;? Specifically, I am interested in how external interventions (e.g. fecal microbiota transplantation, probiotics, or a modified diet) influence microbiome composition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching and mentorship enriched my graduate school experience. While at UCSB I improved my teaching abilities both by studying pedagogy and through practical experience: as a graduate student I was employed as an instructor of record for an upper-division physics course (Summer 2019), a teaching assistant for a freshman-level calculus-based physics course (Fall 2015), and a teaching assistant for an upper-division complex analysis course twice (Winter 2016 and Winter 2020).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
