<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eric W. Jones</title>
    <link>https://erijones.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eric W. Jones</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://erijones.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>My email address is jones.eric93 [at] gmail.com. I would love to talk to anyone interested in learning more about my research.
You can also follow me on twitter at @e_w_jones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/misc/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;! Some text with a link. &amp;ndash;&amp;gt;
The SmartToilet: &amp;ldquo;Dr. John&amp;rdquo; is the gateway to personalized medicine. First place winner of the SFU Postdoc Research Day Writing for the Public Contest. A 250-word research summary prepared for &amp;ldquo;casual science communication pieces for newspapers, magazine articles, blogs, and more for public audiences.&amp;rdquo; Updated 3/31/21.
My SFU Postdoc Research Day Poster. This poster summarizes the theoretical aspects of my thesis (Simplification and control of microbial ecosystems) and also showcases new postdoctoral work studying the role of noise in ecological systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/pictures/</guid>
      <description>Since 2016 I have had the pleasure of through-hiking the Colorado Trail (Fall 2017), the Wonderland Trail (Fall 2019), and the John Muir Trail (Fall 2020). Here are a few pictures from those adventures.
John Muir Trail (Fall 2020)                      
Colorado Trail (Fall 2017)                                            </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Everyone has a gut microbiome, full of trillions of microbes, that influences our health. One person&amp;rsquo;s microbiome might give them a stomach ache, while another person&amp;rsquo;s might help them metabolize food more efficiently. I want to figure out how &amp;ldquo;medicine for the microbiome&amp;rdquo; works&amp;ndash; how can a sick person&amp;rsquo;s microbiome be made &amp;ldquo;healthy&amp;rdquo;? Specifically, I am interested in how external interventions (e.g. fecal microbiota transplantation, probiotics, or a modified diet) influence microbiome composition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching and mentorship enriched my graduate school experience. While at UCSB I improved my teaching abilities both by studying pedagogy and through practical experience: as a graduate student I was employed as an instructor of record for an upper-division physics course (Summer 2019), a teaching assistant for a freshman-level calculus-based physics course (Fall 2015), and a teaching assistant for an upper-division complex analysis course twice (Winter 2016 and Winter 2020).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
