<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>  on </title>
    <link>https://erijones.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in   on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://erijones.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you would like to learn more, or if you would like to join the Jones Microbiome Lab as an undergraduate student, graduate student, or postdoctoral researcher, please reach out to ejones15 [at] uccs.edu.&#xA;Follow us on twitter at @e_w_jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/misc/</guid>
      <description>APS March Meeting 2022 Poster. This poster summarizes my paper &amp;ldquo;Stochastic microbiome assembly depends on context,&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; published in PNAS here. Updated 3/18/22.&#xA;The SmartToilet: &amp;ldquo;Dr. John&amp;rdquo; is the gateway to personalized medicine. First place winner of the SFU Postdoc Research Day Writing for the Public Contest. A 250-word research summary prepared for &amp;ldquo;casual science communication pieces for newspapers, magazine articles, blogs, and more for public audiences.&amp;rdquo; Updated 3/31/21.&#xA;SFU Postdoc Research Day 2021 Poster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pictures</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/pictures/</guid>
      <description>Since 2016 I have had the pleasure of through-hiking the Colorado Trail (Fall 2017), the Wonderland Trail (Fall 2019), and the John Muir Trail (Fall 2020). Here are a few pictures from those adventures.&#xA;John Muir Trail (Fall 2020) Colorado Trail (Fall 2017) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Most people have experienced &amp;ldquo;gut issues&amp;rdquo; that led to diarrhea, discomfort, and other unpleasant symptoms at some point in their lives. In many cases, our gut microbiome&amp;mdash;a complex ecosystem of trillions of bacteria&amp;mdash;has been implicated as a cause of gut maladies. My research is motivated by ``microbiome-based medicine,&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; personalized bacterial therapies that might one day heal suffering individuals. An emblematic and contemporary example of these therapies is fecal microbiota transplantation (FMT), which cures C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://erijones.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://erijones.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching and mentorship enriched my graduate school experience. While at UCSB I improved my teaching abilities both by studying pedagogy and through practical experience: as a graduate student I was employed as an instructor of record for an upper-division physics course (Summer 2019), a teaching assistant for a freshman-level calculus-based physics course (Fall 2015), and a teaching assistant for an upper-division complex analysis course twice (Winter 2016 and Winter 2020).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
